Frontend Developer with +4 years of experience developing Frontend Javascript applications with React.js, Next.js Framework, Redux.js, TailwindCSS, SASS or Bootstrap and Backend with Node.js, express. js and MongoDB, I have great capacity for solving problems related to web, I have developed E-Commerce with payment gateway integration, Landing page, finally I have deployed applications on Vercel, Heroku and AWS platforms, blockchain with Ethers.js, Smart Contracts, Solidity or Binance API and virtual environments with Three.js integrated with blockchain networks

EXPERIENCE

<u>Capital Investment (capitalinvestmenttm.com)</u> Medellín, Antioquia, **Web3 Frontend** —*November, 2021-February, 2023* Front-end Blockchain Developer, Support in project management and analysis of requirements for Web3 and Blockchain applications, integration and implementation with web3.js, ethers.js, MetaMask, Samart Contract or Solidity.

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Vercel, Solidity, Ethers.js Web3.js, Remix, Smart Contracts, Serverless, CI/CD, Design System

BancaCrypto Medellín, Antioquia, Web3 Frontend — October, 2021-November, 2021

Front-end Blockchain Developer, Support in project management and analysis of requirements for Web3 and Blockchain applications, integration and implementation with web3.js, ethers.js, MetaMask, Samart Contract or Solidity.

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Vercel, Solidity, Ethers.js Web3.js, Remix, Smart Contracts, Serverless, CI/CD, Design System

DrakeTech (draketch.ca) Ontario, Canadá, Frontend — September, 2021-October, 2022

Front-end developer, web application layout with Ant Design and Bootstrap, integration with APIs and implementation with React and Redux, support in project management and requirements analysis for software implementation.

Technologies: React.js, Redux,js, Javascript, JSON, JWT, Web API Ant Design, Bootstrap, Git, Git flow, Microfrontend, Design system

Startups Lab - Agencia (startupslabagencia.co), Frontend — August, 2019-Septiembre, 2021

Frontend developer, web page and web application designer and integration of APIs with the Frontend.

- Reduce web site delivery time to the customer by 80% thanks to Vercel
- Reduce layout time by 40% with Tailwind CSS
- Increased development efficiency by 70% thanks to Git flow

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Vercel, Serverless, CI/CD

PROJECTS

Academy- academy-nu.vercel.app - March, 2023

financial courses platform by Bancacrypto.

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, express.js, MongoDB, Vercel, Paytoshi, ethers.js

Paytoshi Commerce – paytoshi-commerce.vercel.app - November, 2022

Test e-commerce to accept cryptocurrencies payments, integrating Paytoshi payment processor.

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, express.js, MongoDB, Vercel, Paytoshi, ethers.js

Personal Portfolio - oquendo.vercel.app - July, 2022

Web portfolio with my information.

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, Vercel

Paytoshi – paytoshi.vercel.app - July, 2022

Test to accept payments with cryptocurrencies, integrating the payment processor.

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, express.js, MongoDB, Vercel, Paytoshi, ethers.js

Capital Investment - capitalinvestmenttm.com - February, 2021

Investments in the cryptocurrency and traditional markets

Technologies: Next.js, React.js, Tailwind CSS, express.js, MongoDB, Vercel, Paytoshi

Cesquant - cesquant.vercel.app - Abril, 2020

financial courses platform.

Sales of courses to customers were optimized by 90%.

Technologies: Next.js React.js, Node.js, express.js, TailwindCSS, AWS S3, Vercel

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Javascript, CSS, SASS, HTML

Frameworks and Tools: Advanced: React, Next.js, Vercel, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, JSON, Web API, Serverless, Design System, Intermediate: Node.js. Git, Gitflow, MongoDB, express.js, AWS, Redux.js, JWT, SASS, CI/CD, Microfrontend, Basic:

Angular 2+, GraphQL, Typescript, Docker, Python

Languages: Español

EDUCATION

Graphic Design, January, 2017 - November, 2018 Instituto Tecnológico San Agustín, Montería - Córdoba

Computer Engineer July, 2011 - July, 2014

Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana, Montería - Córdoba